Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-279. Rules. Baltimore Steam Packet Company
    - Baltimore Steam Packet Company, 1937-1948 (Box 427, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-280. Rules. Port Utilities Commission
    - Port Utilities Commission, 1937-1948 (Box 427, Folder 19)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 427, Folder 20)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 427, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-281. Rules. The New Bedford, Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket Steamboat Line
    - The New Bedford, Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket Steamboat Line, 1937-1956 (Box 427, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-282. Rules. Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 427, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines, 1937-1952 (Box 427, Folder 24)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 427, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 279-283. Rules. Toronto Terminal Warehouses, Limited
    - Toronto Terminal Warehouses, Limited, 1937-1940 (Box 427, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 279-286. Rules. Boston Market Terminal Company
    - Boston Market Terminal Company, 1938-1954 (Box 427, Folder 27)
    - Boston Market Terminal Company vs. John Noonan, 1954 (Box 427, Folder 28)
    - General, 1937-1956 (Box 427, Folder 29)
    - Boston Market Terminal Company, 1942-1943 (Box 427, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 279-287. Rules. Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal Company
    - Vacations, 1950 (Box 427, Folder 31)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 427, Folder 32)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 427, Folder 33)
    - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal Company, 1937-1959 (Box 427, Folder 34)
    - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal Company, 1951-1952 (Box 428, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal Company, 1953 (Box 428, Folder 2)
    - Vacation Dispute, 1950 (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-288. Rules. Water Front Freight Handlers or Long-Shoremen at various Canadian Points
    - Water Front Freight Handlers or Long-Shoremen at various Canadian Points, 1938-1953 (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - Water Front Freight Handlers or Long-Shoremen at various Canadian Points, 1937-1938 (Box 428, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-289. Rules. Dallas Car Interchange and Inspection Bureau
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 428, Folder 6)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 428, Folder 7)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 428, Folder 8)
    - Dallas Car Interchange and Inspection Bureau, 1942 (Box 428, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-290. Rules. Pacific Coast Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 428, Folder 10)
    - Pacific Coast Railway Company, 1938-1955 (Box 428, Folder 11)
    - 1952 Rule Changes; 1955 Health and Welfare, 1953-1956 (Box 428, Folder 12)
    - Pacific Coast Railway Company, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 13)
    - Union Shop, 1951 (Box 428, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 428, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-291. Rules. John Healy Company
    - John Healy Company, 1938-1946 (Box 428, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-292. Rules. Southern Pacific Steamship Lines
    - Southern Pacific Steamship Lines, 1938-1941 (Box 428, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-294. Rules. Troy Union Railroad
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 428, Folder 18)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 428, Folder 19)
    - Troy Union Railroad, 1957 (Box 428, Folder 20)
    - Troy Union Railroad, 1949 (Box 428, Folder 21)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 428, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-294a. Rules. Southern Pacific Steamship Lines
    - Southern Pacific Steamship Lines, 1938 (Box 428, Folder 22a)
  - Sub-Series 279-295. Rules. Union Terminal Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 428, Folder 23)
    - 1953 Rule Changes; 1955 Health and Welfare, 1953-1956 (Box 428, Folder 24)
    - 40 Hour Week -1949-1950 (Box 428, Folder 25)
    - Union Terminal Railway Company, 1944-1953 (Box 428, Folder 26)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 428, Folder 27)
    - Union Terminal Railway Company, 1938-1942 (Box 428, Folder 28)
    - Union Terminal Railway Company, 1941 (Box 428, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 279-296. Rules. Texas Mexican Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 428, Folder 30)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 428, Folder 31)
    - 1953 Rules Changes; 1955 Health and Welfare, 1953-1955 (Box 428, Folder 32)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1952 (Box 429, Folder 1)
    - Texas Mexican Railway Company, 1938-1952 (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - Vacations, 1946 (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Texas Mexican Railway Company, 1945 (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - Texas Mexican Railway Company, 1945 (Box 429, Folder 5)
    - Texas Mexican Railway Company, 1944-1945 (Box 429, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-297. Rules. Luckenbach Steamship Company
    - Luckenbach Steamship Company, 1940 (Box 429, Folder 7)
    - Luckenbach Steamship Company, 1938-1956 (Box 429, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-298. Rules. Southwestern Transportation Company
    - Southwestern Transportation Company, 1938-1941 (Box 429, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-299. Rules. F. W. Nicholas
    - F. W. Nicholas, 1938-1940 (Box 429, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-302. Rules. General Carloading Company Incorporated
    - General Carloading Company Incorporated, 1938-1943 (Box 429, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-303. Rules. Kingston Elevator Company
    - Kingston Elevator Company, 1938-1939 (Box 429, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-304. Rules. Trans-Continental Freight Bureau
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 429, Folder 13)
    - Mediation Case, 1964-1965 (Box 429, Folder 14)
    - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau, 1938-1958 (Box 429, Folder 15)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 429, Folder 16)
    - Vacations, 1943 (Box 429, Folder 17)
    - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau, 1946-1952 (Box 429, Folder 18)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1952 (Box 429, Folder 19)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 429, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-305. Rules. Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad Company
    - Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad Company, 1952-1963 (Box 429, Folder 21)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 429, Folder 22)
    - Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad Company, 1939-1940 (Box 429, Folder 23)
    - Arbitration Case, 1944 (Box 429, Folder 24)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - Vacations, 1942 (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad Company, 1941-1951 (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - Rules Revision, 1945-1947 (Box 430, Folder 4)
    - Rules Revision, 1940-1944 (Box 430, Folder 5)
    - Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad Company, 1942-1945 (Box 430, Folder 6)
    - Arbitration Proceedings, 1944 (Box 430, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-306. Rules. Meraut Service Company
    - Meraut Service Company, 1939 (Box 430, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-307. Rules. Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal
    - 1963 Rules Movement, 1963-1966 (Box 430, Folder 9)
    - General, 1957-1959 (Box 430, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 430, Folder 11)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 430, Folder 12)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 430, Folder 13)
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1953-1956 (Box 430, Folder 14)
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1939-1952 (Box 430, Folder 15)
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1951-1953 (Box 430, Folder 16)
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1951 (Box 430, Folder 17)
    - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1948-1951 (Box 430, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-308. Rules. Union Freight Railroad
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 430, Folder 19)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1952 (Box 430, Folder 20)
    - Union Freight Railroad, 1939-1948 (Box 430, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-309. Rules. Meridian Terminal Company
    - Union Shop, 1953-1957 (Box 430, Folder 22)
    - Meridian Terminal Company, 1949-1964 (Box 430, Folder 23)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1952 (Box 430, Folder 24)
    - Meridian Terminal Company, 1939-1948 (Box 430, Folder 25)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 430, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 279-310. Rules. Railroad Perishable-Inspection Agency
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 430, Folder 27)
    - Railroad Perishable-Inspection Agency, 1945-1952 (Box 430, Folder 28)
    - Railroad Perishable-Inspection Agency, 1949 (Box 430, Folder 29)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - Vacations, 1946-1948 (Box 431, Folder 2)
    - Railroad Perishable-Inspection Agency, 1946-1948 (Box 431, Folder 3)
    - Railroad Perishable-Inspection Agency, 1939-1944 (Box 431, Folder 4)
    - Railroad Perishable-Inspection Agency, 1941 (Box 431, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-311-0. Rules. Motor Carriers. Jacobs Transfer Company
    - General, 1939 (Box 431, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-311-1. Rules. Motor Carriers. Jacobs Transfer Company
    - Jacobs Transfer Company, 1939 (Box 431, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-313. Rules. Rock Island-Frisco Terminal
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 431, Folder 8)
    - 1953 Rule Changes, 1953-1955 (Box 431, Folder 9)
    - General, 1939-1954 (Box 431, Folder 10)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 431, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-314. Rules. Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company
    - 1953 Rules Changes, 1953-1956 (Box 431, Folder 12)
    - General, 1942-1952 (Box 431, Folder 13)
    - Representation Dispute, 1953-1958 (Box 431, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 431, Folder 15)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1957-1958 (Box 431, Folder 16)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1958-1959 (Box 431, Folder 17)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1952-1958 (Box 431, Folder 18)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1955-1956 (Box 431, Folder 19)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1948-1951 (Box 431, Folder 20)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1951 (Box 431, Folder 21)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1945-1946 (Box 431, Folder 22)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1944-1945 (Box 431, Folder 23)
    - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway Company, 1943 (Box 431, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-315. Rules.
    - Rutherford Service Company, 1939-1959 (Box 431, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 279-316. Rules. Stock Yards District Agency
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 1)
    - Stock Yards District Agency, 1953-1955 (Box 432, Folder 2)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1953 (Box 432, Folder 3)
    - Stock Yards District Agency, 1943-1954 (Box 432, Folder 4)
    - Stock Yards District Agency, 1955-1956 (Box 432, Folder 5)
    - Stock Yards District Agency, 1949-1952 (Box 432, Folder 6)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 432, Folder 7)
    - Vacations, 1942-1944 (Box 432, Folder 8)
    - Stock Yards District Agency, 1939-1942 (Box 432, Folder 9)
    - Stock Yards District Agency, 1941-1942 (Box 432, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-317. Rules. North Pacific Coast Freight Bureau
    - 1959 Vacation and Holiday Movement, 1959-1960 (Box 432, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 12)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 432, Folder 13)
    - General, 1939-1954 (Box 432, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 432, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-318. Rules. Toronto Terminals Railway
    - Toronto Terminals Railway, 1939-1949 (Box 432, Folder 16)
    - Toronto Terminals Railway, 1930-1939 (Box 432, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-319. Rules. Chattanooga Station Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 18)
    - Union Shop, 1953-1957 (Box 432, Folder 19)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1952 (Box 432, Folder 20)
    - General, 1939-1953 (Box 432, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-320. Rules. Durham Union Station Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 22)
    - Union Shop, 1957-1958 (Box 432, Folder 23)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1952 (Box 432, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-321. Rules. Columbia Union Station Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 25)
    - Union Shop, 1957-1958 (Box 432, Folder 26)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1952 (Box 432, Folder 26a)
  - Sub-Series 279-322. Rules. Western Warehousing Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 27)
    - 1955 Health and Welfare, 1955-1956 (Box 432, Folder 28)
    - Western Warehousing Company, 1940-1948 (Box 432, Folder 29)
    - Western Warehousing Company, 1940 (Box 432, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 279-323. Rules. Lackawanna and Wyoming Valley Railroad
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 31)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 432, Folder 32)
    - General, 1940-1956 (Box 432, Folder 33)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 432, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 279-324. Rules. Monongahela Connecting Railroad
    - Monongahela Connecting Railroad, 1940-1961 (Box 432, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 279-325. Rules. Texas Electric Railway
    - Texas Electric Railway, 1940-1945 (Box 432, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 279-326. Rules. New York, Susquehanna, and Western Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 432, Folder 37)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 432, Folder 38)
    - New York, Susquehanna, and Western Railroad Company, 1940-1954 (Box 432, Folder 39)
    - New York, Susquehanna, and Western Railroad Company, 1952 (Box 432, Folder 40)
    - Vacations, 1944 (Box 432, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 279-327. Rules. Burlington, Rock Island and Pacific Warehouse, Incorporated
    - Burlington, Rock Island and Pacific Warehouse, Incorporated, 1940-1947 (Box 433, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-328. Rules. Missouri Pacific Freight Transport Company
    - Missouri Pacific Freight Transport Company, 1940-1943 (Box 433, Folder 2)
    - Missouri Pacific Freight Transport Company, 1941-1953 (Box 433, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-329. Rules. Union Motor Coach Terminal Company
    - Strike, 1948 (Box 433, Folder 4)
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company, 1947-1948 (Box 433, Folder 5)
    - Strike, 1947 (Box 433, Folder 6)
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company, 1945-1946 (Box 433, Folder 7)
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company, 1947-1953 (Box 433, Folder 8)
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company, 1937-1944 (Box 433, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-330. Rules. Overland Terminal Warehouse Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 433, Folder 10)
    - Union Shop, 1953 (Box 433, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-331. Rules. Gulf Terminal Company
    - Gulf Terminal Company, 1941-1945 (Box 433, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-332. Rules. Grain Elevator Employees
    - National Harbours Board, Montreal, 1941-1942 (Box 433, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-333. Rules. Atlanta and West Point Railroad
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 433, Folder 14)
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad, 1941-1944 (Box 433, Folder 15)
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad, 1944-1945 (Box 433, Folder 16)
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad, 1942 (Box 433, Folder 17)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 433, Folder 18)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 433, Folder 19)
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad, 1952-1955 (Box 433, Folder 20)
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad, 1942-1949 (Box 433, Folder 21)
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad, 1945-1955 (Box 433, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-334. Rules. Spokane International Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434, Folder 1)
    - General, 1941-1954 (Box 434, Folder 2)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 434, Folder 3)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 434, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-335. Rules. New Orleans and Lower Coast Railroad
    - New Orleans and Lower Coast Railroad, 1950-1957 (Box 434, Folder 5)
    - New Orleans and Lower Coast Railroad, 1943-1950 (Box 434, Folder 6)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 434, Folder 7)
    - New Orleans and Lower Coast Railroad, 1941-1942 (Box 434, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-336. Rules. Detroit and Cleveland Navigation Company
    - Detroit and Cleveland Navigation Company, 1946-1951 (Box 434, Folder 9)
    - Detroit and Cleveland Navigation Company, 1941-1945 (Box 434, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-338. Rules. National Trailways Bus Depot
    - National Trailways Bus Depot, 1953-1962 (Box 434, Folder 11)
    - National Trailways Bus Depot, 1941-1952 (Box 434, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-339. Rules. Fort Dodge, Des Moines, and Southern Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434, Folder 13)
    - Fort Dodge, Des Moines, and Southern Railway Company, 1957-1958 (Box 434, Folder 14)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 434, Folder 15)
    - Fort Dodge, Des Moines, and Southern Railway Company, 1941-1956 (Box 434, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-340. Rules. Augusta Union Station Company
    - General, 1941-1955 (Box 434, Folder 17)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434, Folder 18)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 434, Folder 19)
    - Augusta Union Station Company, 1944-1945 (Box 434, Folder 20)
    - Augusta Union Station Company, 1942 (Box 434, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-341. Rules. Parmelee Transportation Company
    - Parmelee Transportation Company, 1955-1956 (Box 434, Folder 22)
    - Union Shop, 1953 (Box 434, Folder 23)
    - Parmelee Transportation Company, 1941-1954 (Box 434, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-342. Rules. Eastern Abattoirs Limited, Montreal
    - Eastern Abattoirs Limited, Montreal, 1941 (Box 434, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 279-343. Rules. Ashley, Drew, and Northern Railway Company
    - Ashley, Drew, and Northern Railway Company, 1948-1953 (Box 434, Folder 26)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434a, Folder 1)
    - Ashley, Drew, and Northern Railway Company, 1941-1948 (Box 434a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-344. Rules. Fruit Growers Express Company
    - Fruit Growers Express Company, 1941-1944 (Box 434a, Folder 3)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 434a, Folder 3a)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434a, Folder 4)
    - Fruit Growers Express Company, 1946-1950 (Box 434a, Folder 4a)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 434a, Folder 5)
    - Vacations, 1944-1950 (Box 434a, Folder 5a)
    - Fruit Growers Express Company, 1945-1950 (Box 434a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-345. Rules. Fonda, Johnstown, and Gloversville Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434a, Folder 7)
    - Fonda, Johnstown, and Gloversville Railroad Company, 1941-1951 (Box 434a, Folder 8)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 434a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-346. Rules. Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434a, Folder 10)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 434a, Folder 11)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad Company, 1945-1946 (Box 434a, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad Company, 1941-1942 (Box 434a, Folder 13)
    - General, 1942-1955 (Box 434a, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad Company, 1948-1950 (Box 434a, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-347. Rules. Norfolk Terminal Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434a, Folder 16)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1952 (Box 434a, Folder 17)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 434a, Folder 18)
    - Norfolk Terminal Railway Company, 1943 (Box 434a, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-348. Rules. Canada Atlantic Transit Company of the United States
    - Canada Atlantic Transit Company of the United States, 1941-1942 (Box 434a, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-349. Rules. Denver Union Stock Yard Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 434a, Folder 21)
    - Denver Union Stock Yard Company, 1941-1957 (Box 434a, Folder 22)
    - Denver Union Stock Yard Company, 1941-1955 (Box 434a, Folder 23)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 434a, Folder 24)
    - Denver Union Stock Yard Company, 1947-1948 (Box 434a, Folder 25)
    - Denver Union Stock Yard Company, 1942-1943 (Box 435, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-350. Rules. Lake Terminal Railroad Company
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1956-1962 (Box 435, Folder 2)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1949-1950 (Box 435, Folder 3)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1948-1949 (Box 435, Folder 4)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1944-1945 (Box 435, Folder 5)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1951-1952 (Box 435, Folder 6)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 435, Folder 7)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1947-1950 (Box 435, Folder 8)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1949-1950 (Box 435, Folder 9)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1942-1944 (Box 435, Folder 10)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1942-1943 (Box 435, Folder 11)
    - General, 1942-1955 (Box 435, Folder 12)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 435, Folder 13)
    - Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1954-1957 (Box 435, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 435, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-351. Rules. Georgia and Florida Railway
    - Georgia and Florida Railway, 1957-1962 (Box 435, Folder 16)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 435, Folder 17)
    - Georgia and Florida Railway, 1941-1957 (Box 435, Folder 18)
    - Georgia and Florida Railway, 1942-1946 (Box 435, Folder 19)
    - Georgia and Florida Railway, 1952-1953 (Box 435, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-352. Rules. Lehigh and Hudson River Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 1)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 436, Folder 2)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 436, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-353. Rules. Davenport, Rock Island, and Northwestern Railway
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 436, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-354. Rules. Spokane Union Station
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 436, Folder 5)
    - Spokane Union Station, 1948 (Box 436, Folder 6)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 436, Folder 7)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-355. Rules. East Portland Freight Terminal
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 9)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 436, Folder 10)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 436, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-356. Rules. Cleveland Union Terminal
    - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1957 (Box 436, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Case, 1961 (Box 436, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 436, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-357. Rules. Royal Netherlands Steamship Company
    - Royal Netherlands Steamship Company, 1941-1942 (Box 436, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-358. Rules. Baltimore and Ohio-New York Terminals
    - Baltimore and Ohio-New York Terminals, 1941-1947 (Box 436, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-359. Rules. Baltimore and Ohio-Chicago Terminal Railroad Company
    - Baltimore and Ohio-Chicago Terminal Railroad Company, 1942-1943 (Box 436, Folder 18)
    - Baltimore and Ohio-Chicago Terminal Railroad Company. General, 1941-1951 (Box 436, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-360. Rules. Pittsburgh Joint Stock Yards Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 20)
    - Pittsburgh Joint Stock Yards Company, 1937-1945 (Box 436, Folder 21)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 436, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-361. Rules. Terminal Storage Company of Washington, D.C.
    - Terminal Storage Company of Washington, D.C., 1941 (Box 436, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-362. Rules. Tampa Union Station
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 436, Folder 24)
    - Tampa Union Station, 1939-1951 (Box 436, Folder 25)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 26)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 436, Folder 27)
    - Vacations, 1946 (Box 436, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 279-363. Rules. Hannibal Union Depot
    - Hannibal Union Depot, 1941-1955 (Box 436, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 279-365. Rules. Pittsburgh, Chartiers, and Youghiogheny Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 30)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 436, Folder 31)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 436, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 279-366. Rules. Akron Union Passenger Depot Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 33)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 436, Folder 34)
    - Vacations, 1950 (Box 436, Folder 35)